Bateson Family Papers 1829-1940 Mss.Ms.Coll.2
American Philosophical Society
- Bateson Family Papers, 1829-1940; 2.0 Linear feet
  - To and from William Bateson, 1922; Wilson, Grace (Box 4)
    Re: Martin Bateson suicide and legacy.